Denis Tovstokhatko

Frontend Developer

Personal summary

Hey! I'm Denis - a self-educated and enthusiastic front-end developer from Kyiv.

I consider myself as a person who always moves forward to new opportunities, knowledge and experiences that is why I am extremely interested in web development, which has already equipped me with skills and attitudes required for a successful professional career.

Believe in producing high-quality work, that fuels the engagement between WEB and his audience. Passions - music, sport and technology.

Works: https://dentov13.github.io/

Career History

January 2017 - September 2017 (9 month)

HTML Coder / Frontend Developer

Skywell LLC - skywell.com.ua

February 2016 - December 2016 (11 month)

Web-developer

Audit firm "Alliance" - alliance.co.ua

October 2015 - December 2015 (3 month)

Trainee / Junior Frontend Developer

IT-Mentor — pet-project from community of dou.ua

Education

November 2016 - January 2017

JavaScript Advanced course (Certificate), CBS

August 2016 - Winter 2017-2018 (in progress)

Master in Computer Science, KNUTE

September 2012 - June 2016

Bachelor in Economic Cybernetics, KNUTE

Skills

- HTML 5, CSS 3
- SASS / SCSS
- PostCSS
- BEM methodology
- Bootstrap
- Git
- jQuery
- JavaScript (ES5 / ES6)
- AJAX
- Babel
- ReactJS
- Redux
- React Router
- RamdaJS
- Gulp, Webpack
- Bower
- Node.js (basic)
- npm / yarn
- WordPress (inc. backend)
- PHP

Other Skills

- Adobe Photoshop / Sketch
- Avocode / Zeplin
- Github / Bitbucket
- Terminal
- Cross-browser development
- Technical curiosity
- Affinity for detail
- Intermediate English

Contacts

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

Birthday: 13 October 1995

Mobile: +380(93) 019 05 40

Portfolio: dentov13.github.io

Mail: tovstokhatko.denis@gmail.com







